Elena Sacristán Sacristán

66 Irwell Estate, Neptune Street, SE16 7JS - London Mobile: 07710 263790 - Email: elenitta1983@yahoo.es

PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I am an experienced Survey Scripter who has been working in Marketing Research for more than 8 years with excellent technical qualifications, strong IT expertise and a wide range of practical skills.

I am an organized, efficient, hard working and flexible individual with the ability to achieve tasks when working alone or as part of a team.

KEY SKILLS

TECHNICAL SKILLS SUMMARY

- Marketing Research Platforms: Confirmit, SurveyGizmo, OfficeReports and Results.
- Databases: Advanced Excel skills, experience working with DBF tables using Advantage Data Architect and basic knowledge of SPSS.
- Programming languages: HTML, CSS, SQL, C, C++ and Assembly for Microprocessors 68000 Motorola and 68H.
- General Software: Microsoft Office, Adobe Acrobat.
- Graphic Design: Adobe Photoshop, Fireworks, Illustrator, In Design and AutoCAD.
- Operative Systems: MS-DOS, Windows XP, Windows Vista, Windows 7 and Mac OS.

LANGUAGES

- Spanish: Native language
- English: Fluent to a level suitable for business.
- **Interpersonal skills:** Proven ability to communicate on all levels from instructing less experienced staff to taking part in meetings with Directors, Management and Clients.
- Organizational: Effective at time management and prioritizing tasks to achieve deadlines.
- Attention to detail: I have developed this skill even more in my current job since data consistence and accuracy are essential and there are many procedures that need to be executed thoroughly to ensure the quality of the tasks.
- A committed team player: Working in a small company with very tight deadlines where good communication within the team is essential in order to deliver the projects on time.
- Well-motivated, responsible, energetic and flexible individual who enjoys the challenges of meeting deadlines and works well under pressure.
- Fast learner, who is very keen on enhancing my own technical skills as well as learning new ones.

CAREER HISTORY

August 2015 – current position Senior Survey Scripter

Fusion Insight & Strategy, London

- Scripting surveys in Confirmit and SurveyGizmo.
- Applying amends suggested by clients or researchers to surveys and reports.
- Creating themes for surveys to match the branding from the client (Fireworks, Photoshop, HTML, CSS).
- Cleaning and preparing sample files to be uploaded into Confirmit or SurveyGizmo.
- Creating reports with Reportal using different banners to segment the responses and help researchers to analyze the data.
- Working on automation of recurring tasks to help us being more efficient (i.e. Excel macros, survey templates).
- Working of automation of PowerPoint presentations.
- Export, Import and re-code data from different surveys platforms.
- Improving the look and feel of online surveys in desktop mode and mobile.

June 2009 – August 2015 Sampling/DP Executive (Data Processing Team)

Ronin Corporation, London

- Using SQL queries to analyze and update databases maintaining high quality data deliverables.
- Analyzing databases and effectively trouble shooting data queries and inconsistencies.
- Providing suggestions and solutions to constantly improve the Data Processing processes and procedures.
- Updating reports in Java, HTML and CLIPPER.

- Updating stored procedures written in SQL.
- Uploading Samples into Results and Confirmit Surveys.
- Setting up WEB and CATI jobs in both Results and Confirmit for internal or externally hosted surveys.
- Setting up jobs for Outsource companies (implementing re-direct links, creating re-direct documents, capturing/sending variables).
- Setting up and sending emails to the sample loaded in the surveys (Confirmit and Results).
- Working closely with Project Managers to accommodate their requests and in order to suggest different set ups depending on the jobs.

April 2007 - October 2008

Team Leader

Alfonso Benitez S.A. (group FCC S.A.) Madrid, Spain

- Representing one of the biggest Spanish Companies in Services, managing the cleaning contract of two districts in Madrid.
- Dealing directly with the client (city council) by phone and sending daily reports.
- Responsible for H&S and environmental matters, ensuring we complied with regulations.
- Managing 6 recycling points which involves dealing with disposal of toxic waste and setting up removal dates amongst other tasks.
- Monthly meetings with The Union Representatives Committee to deal with everything in relation with the workers.
- Quarterly meetings with H&S experts and the director of the company in order to improve many aspects within the
 organization.

Sept 2006 - April 2007 Technical Electronic Engineer

SICA S.A, Madrid, Spain

- Working as part of a team in which our aim was the design and installation of control and supervision systems for electrical substations.
- The majority of the clients were railway companies such as METRO (Underground of Madrid) or AVE RENFE (long distance rail services), but I also provided services to different companies such as TVE (National Spanish TV Channel).
- My role was to communicate the PLC's with the SCADA's, creating the SCADA interface and drawing the designs with AutoCAD. I also took part in the programming of Siemens PLC's (S7-300 and S7-400).
- I operated under very strict deadlines in which good communication within the team was very important, as the deliverables were interconnected.

EDUCATION AND QUALIFICATIONS

September 2001- June 2006

Universidad de Alcalá, Alcalá de Henares, Madrid (Spain).

B Eng Electronic Engineering

*As a result of my good performance during my degree the Universidad de Alcalá awarded me with an Erasmus grant (Sep 05-Jun. 06) to end my degree in Ireland where I completed the final project

* September 2005- June 2006

Letterkenny Institute of Technology, Letterkenny (Ireland).

B Eng Electronic Engineering Final Project:

"Design and Implementation of a Training System of Athletics, Based in Radio Communication"

ADDITIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

February 2017 Introduction to Java Script

London Academy of IT (London)

April 2014 Web Design with HTML and CSS

London Academy of IT (London)

April 2010 - June 2010 Certificate in Graphic Design

. Waes (London)

September 2008 – April 2009 Distance learning: Certificate in Health and Safety

Hed<u>ima (</u>Madrid, Spain)

INTERESTS AND ACTIVITIES

During my holidays I enjoy volunteering and traveling.

In my spare time I like to play Volleyball and Beach Volleyball and at present I'm competing in the London Premier League and in the 1st division of National League.